MICHELLE LE

(316) 214-0954 michtn.le@gmail.com My LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With over seven years of diverse customer service experience spanning various industries, I have consistently delivered exemplary customer service marked by clarity, timeliness, and accuracy. My expertise extends to effectively managing the implementation of intricate projects, showcasing a keen ability to balance multiple tasks simultaneously.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

R1 Revenue Cycle Management, Manhattan KS

August 2023 - Current

Patient Access Representative

- I consistently registered an average of 75 patients daily, ensuring meticulous verification of demographics, insurance coverage, benefits, and obtaining necessary pre-certifications, referrals, or authorizations in adherence to insurance company requirements.
- I adeptly balanced three hospital programs MediTech, Phressia, and R1Hub ensuring accurate recording patients accounts for admissions, physicians, and nurses to document.
- Addressing customer concerns with empathy, I resolved issues promptly and direct unresolved matters to the appropriate department.
- Upholding the highest standards, I maintained the confidentiality, security, and integrity of patient information in accordance with hospital policies and procedures.

Hy-Vee, Manhattan KS

October 2021 - October 2022

Starbucks Shift Supervisor

- Selected as the Employee of the Year 2021, I earned this recognition through my optimistic, gogetter attitude, and a remarkable track record of high customer retention rate.
- In my role, I effectively delegated store operations standards, ensuring the consistent delivery of the Starbucks Experience.
- I meticulously recorded all cash transactions, maintaining precision in adherence to Starbucks and Hy-Vee accounting guidelines.
- Proactively anticipating customer and store needs, I continuously evaluated and accessed the environment, leading to a notable increase in customer satisfaction and retention.

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry, CareerFoundry.com

November 2021 - Current

Graduated: December 2020

User Experience and Interface Designer

Kansas State University, Manhattan KS

Bachelor of Science - Mechanical Engineering

Cumulative GPA: 3.15

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office 365, Figma, Python, SolidWorks